## Amrita De

CONTACT

11/13,Vivekananda Road,Satabdi Seoraphuly,Hooghly West Bengal,712223 **E-mail:** deamrita2015@gmail.com **Website:** <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/amrita-de-">https://www.linkedin.com/in/amrita-de-</a>

8109b2125, https://github.com/deamrita

**Phone:** 8777757784

**OBJECTIVE** 

Currently pursuing MSc. in Analytics from Tata Institute of Social Sciences, Mumbai. To equip myself with more expertise with a growth-oriented position in an organization where my technical skills will be further developed and utilized along with the organization's growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Tata Consultancy Services**

June 2019 — Aug 2021

System Engineer

- Created reports by joining multiple tables from multiples database using complex SQL queries
- Analyzed massive and highly complex data sets, performing ad-hoc analysis and data manipulation.
- Coding in PL/SQL for new developments and Code enhancements across various modules in Oracle Human Resource Management System.
- End to end development, requirements gathering, Configuration, Coding, Testing, Debugging, Documentation of techno-functional components for several implementation projects.
- Monitored and implemented bi-weekly changes. Played significant role in supporting System testing and User Acceptance Testing.
- Interacting with users to understand their problems and providing them timely better solutions with zero customer escalation.
- Working in a offshore-onshore model. Maintaining and managing co-ordination in the team.

SUMMER TRAINING

## Android Development trainee | Globsyn technologies Jun 2018 - AUG 2018

Worked on different design languages under Android API level 27, Managing API implementation and Material design 2.0 migration, Firebase solution for android application backend.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS/ TECHNOLOGY/ TOOLS

- SQL
- Python
- MS Excel
- Oracle PL/SQL
- ORACLE E-Business Suit
- Human capital Management
- Service-Now Monitoring
- Oracle RDBMS
- Android Studio
- OOP Java
- Data Structure and Algorithm
- C

Amrita De

FINAL YEAR PROJECT

Seeker: An android application that generates live captions depending upon the content of the viewfinder (API 27, Material Design 2.0)

**EDUCATION** 

MSc. in Analytics

Aug 2021 — May 2023

Tata Institute of Social Sciences

Bachelor of Technology on Computer Science and Engineering

Aug 2015 — June 2019

Government College of Engineering and Textile Technology, Serampore

Obtained the B.Tech degree with DGPA 8.93

**Higher Secondary** 

May 2013 — May 2015

Serampore Girls High School

Percentage of Marks 90.4

Madhyamik

May 2012 — May 2013

Serampore Girls High School

Percentage of Marks 89.0

CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAININGS

 Oracle E-Business Suite R12 Human Capital Management Certified Implementation Specialist with 95% remarks. [Oracle Technologies, December 2020]

## **INTERESTS**

- Passionate about new technology.
- Avid reader.
- Listening to music.
- Digital Painting.

AWARDS AND ACCOMPLISHME NTS

- Star of the Month December 2020.
- Received multiple appreciations and recognitions from customers and colleagues for technical expertise, quick learning and prompt solution providing.

Amrita De 2